#### Contact

spolisettirn@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sharanyapersaud-bsn-rn-bc-ccrn-82901696 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Geriatrics

Mental Health

Public Health

### Certifications

ACLS

BLS

Medical-Surgical Nursing (RN-BC)

**PALS** 

**CCRN** 

# Sharanya Persaud, BSN, RN-BC, CCRN

Assistant Nurse Manager, Cardiac Cath Lab at Staten Island University Hospital

Greater New York City Area

## Summary

Assistant Nurse Manager of Cardiac Cath Lab; Pursuing MS in Nursing. Strong background in Nursing including experience in medical-surgical areas, telemetry, public health nursing, home care consulting, and Preop/PACU. Member of the Sigma Theta Tau International Honor society of Nursing, Nursing Informatics committee, Unit practice Council, Policy committee, and Retention, Recruitment and Recognition committee at NYP.

## Experience

Staten Island University Hospital
Assistant Nurse Manager, Cardiac Cath Lab
August 2019 - Present (10 months)
Staten Island, New York

New York-Presbyterian Hospital 4 years 6 months

Per diem Pre-op RN August 2019 - Present (10 months)

Greater New York City Area

Preop/Postop RN April 2018 - July 2019 (1 year 4 months) Greater New York City Area

PACU RN

February 2017 - April 2018 (1 year 3 months)

Staff Nurse

December 2015 - February 2017 (1 year 3 months)

Lincoln Tech - Edison

Clinical Instructor (Part Time)
March 2017 - Present (3 years 3 months)

Staten Island University Hospital Registered Nurse May 2013 - November 2015 (2 years 7 months)

Visiting Nurse Service of New York 3 years 3 months

Public Health Nurse
April 2013 - September 2015 (2 years 6 months)
Per Diem Public Health Nurse in Staten Island

Home Care Consultant July 2012 - April 2013 (10 months)

Seaview rehabilitation center and home Registered Nurse June 2011 - April 2013 (1 year 11 months)

### Education

CUNY College of Staten Island
Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing · (2007 - 2012)

Chamberlain University

Master of Science (M.S.), Nursing (2016 - 2019)